<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fedora on Sahil&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>http://www.sahil.cc/tags/fedora/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fedora on Sahil&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please mention source if you want to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 01:11:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sahil.cc/tags/fedora/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a super-pendrive</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2009/creating-a-super-pendrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 01:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2009/creating-a-super-pendrive/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
Its been really long since I blogged. Before going ahead, want to tell you that will be posting my endeavours on running virtual machines soon.
This, however, is my experience/guide for creating a super pen drive (a.k.a. a usb disk that if booted from presents a grub menu with options - GParted, Fedora, .. and any other linux distro hopefully, and has Fedora persistence, and has a spare partition too for you to use it as a normal pen drive).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Fedora rpms/yum work - Offline</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2009/making-fedora-work-offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2009/making-fedora-work-offline/</guid>
      <description>This is guide relevant to those who wish to spread fedora to friends and loved ones who don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily always have an internet connection (or a good one atleast). The problem faced in such situations, almost always (talking from my experience), is that there are a huge number of rpms that need to be downloaded to make fedora capable of playing media, and fill it with good stuff like k3b, amarok etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 9 Released!!!</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/fedora-9-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 16:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/fedora-9-released/</guid>
      <description>And it rocks!!
The first thing you notice after fedora 9 is the blazing faaaast startup and shutdown times.
Now, before I say anything else about Fedora 9, here are a few screenshots :
Here&amp;rsquo;s Gnome in F9 :
   Gnome Preview    And here is KDE 4 (finally !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things done in college - technology</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/things-done-in-college-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/things-done-in-college-technology/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of things I have done in the past three years. I have written for the sake of personal record.
As a member of Delta : Created a &amp;ldquo;PC Based Oscilloscope&amp;rdquo; in IIT Bombay, as a summer project. Used java servlets on the server side and a java applet on the client side. Was responsible for the whole of the software side - 2006 Summers Worked in Pragyan CMS V1, which finally got implemented in our college website - 2005-2007 Made Dalal Street, a stock market simulator using java servlets on the server side and using eclipse to make a java based ui compiled using gcj to eliminate the need of jvm to run the final executable - 2006 Dec - 2007 Jan Used CVS for the development of Dalal Street, understood the importance of a code versioning system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating your own schemas in FDS Ldap for use in postfix (or anything else for that matter) :P</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/creating-your-own-schemas-in-fds-ldap-for-use-in-postfix-or-anything-else-for-that-matter-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 15:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/creating-your-own-schemas-in-fds-ldap-for-use-in-postfix-or-anything-else-for-that-matter-p/</guid>
      <description>What I needed for mailman like functioning while making postfix work with ldap was an attribute that stores content of type DN (Distinguished Name) i.e. a node address, or holding a data type that stores nothing but data of type that can hold address of the data type itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mail with postfix and ldap</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/mail-with-postfix-and-ldap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 08:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/mail-with-postfix-and-ldap/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s possible. I did it for the pragyan.org server.
The setup we used was :
 /var/mail/virtual/%u: the inboxes of different users, /var/mail/virtual/PragyanMail/%u/%f: the different folders in mailboxes of different users.  It&amp;rsquo;s much easily setup than one thinks initially.
HOW?? Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
But, as with anything else, basics first
 SMTP server : Simple Mail Transfer Protocol : The server which sends and receives mails. Postfix (or smtp).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Directory Server Rocks!!!</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/fedora-directory-server-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 01:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/fedora-directory-server-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Having gone through the hell of installing an LDAP server once, I thought I could I could install the openldap server on the old server that we had to shift to.
Anshu had already broken his head on it and was at the verge of losing his sanity. And so i stepped in.
First I checked /etc/openldap/slapd.conf, line by line. Everything was fine. ldapadd -W -x -D &amp;quot;cn=Manager,dc=pragyan,dc=org&amp;quot; -f base.ldif **invalid credentials (49)**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programs like these make life easy - Fedora Frog</title>
      <link>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2006/programs-like-these-make-life-easy-fedora-frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2006 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sahil.cc/post/2006/programs-like-these-make-life-easy-fedora-frog/</guid>
      <description>Man!! This really is great! Here is what the site says - &amp;gt; Fedora Frog is GUI install script that jumps your Fedora Core 5 to life in no time&amp;hellip; Fedora Frog supports 32 bit installations, some parts may work also on 64 bit installations. This script installs most of the stuff you will ever need to get things really working in Fedora Core 5. Here&amp;rsquo;s what it can do (Hold your breath!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>