<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faridabad on Sahil&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://www.sahil.cc/tags/faridabad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faridabad on Sahil&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please mention source if you want to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 11:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.sahil.cc/tags/faridabad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gods must be crazy..</title>
      <link>https://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/the-gods-must-be-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 11:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sahil.cc/post/2008/the-gods-must-be-crazy/</guid>
      <description>Really.
I mean, this is Faridabad.. in MAY!!! Last year this time, it was blazing hot with loo making it&amp;rsquo;s rounds all over India, with people dying of brain fever.
And now, when I come to Faridabad for 10 days, the last time before my job starts, the weather decides to become stormy, windy and rainy.
I caught a throat infection while coming home via Bhilai from NIT Trichy. I was hoping the heat here would cure the infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to square one</title>
      <link>https://www.sahil.cc/post/2007/back-to-square-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 19:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sahil.cc/post/2007/back-to-square-one/</guid>
      <description>I am back home at Faridabad now.
It was a great journey form Trichy to here. Me and Ankit came together. We caught Rockfort express from Trichy and reached Chennai around 5:30 in the morning. Once we got down the train, we leisurely checked the time for our next train - Gareeb Rath. We had to go from Chennai Egmore station to Chennai Central station to catch the train. And the time for the departure of the train wasss&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>