<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ldap on Sahil&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>http://test.sahil.cc/tags/ldap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ldap on Sahil&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 02:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://test.sahil.cc/tags/ldap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Things done in college - technology</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/things-done-in-college-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/things-done-in-college-technology/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of things I have done in the past three years. I have written for the sake of personal record.
As a member of Delta : Created a &amp;ldquo;PC Based Oscilloscope&amp;rdquo; in IIT Bombay, as a summer project. Used java servlets on the server side and a java applet on the client side. Was responsible for the whole of the software side - 2006 Summers Worked in Pragyan CMS V1, which finally got implemented in our college website - 2005-2007 Made Dalal Street, a stock market simulator using java servlets on the server side and using eclipse to make a java based ui compiled using gcj to eliminate the need of jvm to run the final executable - 2006 Dec - 2007 Jan Used CVS for the development of Dalal Street, understood the importance of a code versioning system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LDAP authentication through Apache for svn, trac or anything else for that matter :P</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/ldap-authentication-through-apache-for-svn-trac-or-anything-else-for-that-matter-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 02:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/ldap-authentication-through-apache-for-svn-trac-or-anything-else-for-that-matter-p/</guid>
      <description>Apache can be used as an access method for things like svn, trac, and even a whole file system through webdav. And apache also supports authentication through LDAP. Hence Apache can be used to authenticate the services that it provides through LDAP.
Here is how it is done :
For SVN :
&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; ServerName repos.nitt.edu DocumentRoot &amp;quot;/var/www/svn/DocumentRoot/&amp;quot; ErrorLog logs/repos.nitt.edu-error_log CustomLog logs/repos.nitt.edu-access_log combined &amp;lt;Location /pragyan&amp;gt; DAV svn SVNPath /var/www/svn/pragyan &amp;lt;LimitExcept OPTIONS REPORTGET&amp;gt; AuthType Basic AuthBasicProvider ldap AuthzLDAPAuthoritative off AuthName &amp;quot;Pragyan SVN LDAP Authentication&amp;quot; AuthLDAPURL ldap://localhost:389/ou=Pragyan,dc=www,dc=nitt,dc=edu?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>