<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sahil&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>http://test.sahil.cc/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sahil&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 23:56:14 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://test.sahil.cc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching From Hexo to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/switching-from-hexo-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 23:56:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/switching-from-hexo-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>This is the first hugo blog post.
Crazy time trying to figure out differences sections, types and layouts.
Finally the dust settles, with a few compromises.
TODOs Need to add tags apart from just categories in the template. A nice challenge! Need to figure out shortcodes for youtube and fontawesome. (About us page dependent on that) To figure out how to publish to sahil.cc (to a separate github repo to allow https) Using image in Hugo Deciding folder and URL structure of posts Finalize default archetype Copy all posts  Learnings Categorization: Categorization of posts in happen through two concepts:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Unicode Characters in Ubuntu</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/typing-unicode-characters-in-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 23:20:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/typing-unicode-characters-in-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I decided that &amp;#96; was he best means to toggle Yakuake (which has been my lifeline for an integral part of the way I work for a long time now), typing &amp;#96; whenever I needed it has been hell.
After going through a great deal and self doubt, the final outcome deserves being documented.
The way to type a backtick without using the backtick key is through its unicode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github 2016 Report Card</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/github-2016-report-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 12:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2017/github-2016-report-card/</guid>
      <description> My 2016 Commits A great tool https://githubreportcard.reflect.io/ helped me visualize the same in more detail: In comparison to 2015 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 13:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/quotes/</guid>
      <description>Hello World
 Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about people stealing your ideas. If your ideas are any good, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to ram them down people&amp;rsquo;s throats.
 ― Howard Aiken, from the book &amp;ldquo;Steal Like an Artist&amp;rdquo;
 What is originality? Undetected plagiarism
 ― William Ralph Inge, from the book &amp;ldquo;Steal Like an Artist&amp;rdquo;
 Documentation should always be written with the assumption that only the examples are read.
 ― Prakhar Srivastav</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>public_html web server - without mod_userdir</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/public-html-web-server-without-mod-userdir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 08:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/post/2008/public-html-web-server-without-mod-userdir/</guid>
      <description>Hell, what does the title mean??
It means this :
Allow people to put files in the public_html folder in their home directories and allow it to be seen through the web server of that server in this format : http://servername/~username/hisorherfiles
Most people use mod_userdir to allow ~username directories in their webservers. However, there is simple rewrite rule workaround that eliminates the need for mod_userdir. I needed this because we had the home directories on the server, but the users had no login accounts on the server and they needed their public_html to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/about/index-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 04:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/about/index-2/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog about how Nitin Isloorkar, Sumit Mathur and I went 2006 about our summer project in IIT Bombay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://test.sahil.cc/about/index-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://test.sahil.cc/about/index-1/</guid>
      <description>I am a freak, an atheist, a thinker, a problem sniffer, a workaholic, a music nerd, a free software advocate, a virus, a bathroom singer, a woman lover, a photographer, a chess player, an idiot, a clown, and alive.
I was born in 1987 at Ahmedabad, Gujrat (India). The part after that gets very confusing. So, I have organized the names of the places I have lived in (for myself):   Place Period School   Ahmedabad 7 yrs Thumblina (Nursery, KG1 KG2), St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>